Star Health's Assure Plan and Aditya Barla's
Active One Plan are these two plans
better than the ICICI Loard Elevate Plan.
We can't just decide this.
Therefore, in today's video, we are going to
compare all three plans. First, we will
understand the eligibility conditions of all three plans. Then, point by point,
we will differentiate their coverage and benefits.
Which
feature is more in each plan, which coverage you
get more. After that, we will understand the ads,
which plan offers how much advance, and
how you can modify your policy. At the
end of the video, I will
also share my opinion about what shortcomings
I find in all three plans after this comparison
and what are the
special features of these plans. The video does not end here.
We will
also compare the prices in this video so that
you can check their affordability in a single video
and you will know which of these three
plans will cost you less. So, if
you are Star Health Assure  Are you
confused between the Sasi Lombard Elevate Plan and the Aditya Barella Active One Next Plan, or are you thinking of taking it,
or want to port your policy,
or are an advisor or agent and
want to understand these for your clients' knowledge, then today's
video will clear all your doubts, so let's
not delay and quickly
start the video. The first point in this is the
entry age. If we talk about the
entry age of ICICI Lombard, then the
entry age for adults is from 18 years to 125 years, that
is, there is no capping on maximum entries.
If we talk about dependent children, then
they can take ICICI Lombard plan from 91 days to 30 years.
If dependent children, that is, come under a family floater policy with their parents, then
they can take individual plans even till a higher age.
Now let's talk about the Star
Assure plan, here the
entry age for adults is from 18 years to  75
years, 18 years to 75 years and the
age of the dependent child is 91 days to 17 years, that is, the
dependent children will
remain in the policy for a maximum of 17 years, after that they will have to pay the
premium of an adult, however,
if they are in this policy as a dependent child, then
they get a discount of up to 40% on their premium. Now
comes the turn of Aditya Birla Active One Next
variant, so here the
entry age for adults is from 18 years to a
maximum, there is no capping, that is, there is no
age limit, but
for dependent children,
those children who are from 91 days to 25 years, in this policy, the age of a
dependent child can live with their parents.
Talking about renewal, all three
plans
provide you the facility of lifelong renewal irrespective of these entry ages and
if we talk about the plan type, individual or
family floater, then you can take both types of policies
in all these three plans. Now
friends, let's talk  The sum insured means
how much coverage you
can take in all these three plans, so in IIC Lord
Elevate plan the coverage starts from ₹ lakh
and you can take maximum coverage up to ₹ crore
where your sum insured
is fixed but if you want there to be no
limit on your sum insured, if that is the case then
you can also choose the option of unlimited sum insured
in IIC Lord Elevate plan.
Now let's talk about Star
Asher plan, here
you are given flexible options from ₹ lakh to ₹ crore
and in Aditya Bala Active One
Next variant also
you can choose sum insured from ₹ lakh to ₹ crore
and if you choose the higher variants of Aditya Bala Active One
like Max, Max, Vital, Saver
or VIP VIP Plus then there
you can also get sum insured up to 6 crore.
Options are available. Talking about tenure,
you can take a long-term policy of up to 3 years in all three plans.
You
can also take a 2-year policy simultaneously. If you
pay a premium for more than 1 year, the
insurance company also gives you a long-term
discount. Now, let's talk about whether there is a
single standard variant in these plans
or are there many variants available within it.
Talking about the ICICI Lord
Elevate plan, there
is only one standard plan here, but the insurance company
gives you two options: a basic plan in which
you can add ads as per your wish,
and an essential pack in which
five ads are already added. You
can choose from these two options. The Star Asher
plan has only one variant, while the
Aditya Bala Active One, which is the next variant, is
a variant. If we talk about the Active One plan, there are a
total of seven variants
available here, which you can choose according to your coverage.
Now, after understanding the eligibility,
friends, it is time to understand the coverage and
benefits one by one.  We will
take points and compare across the plans to see
if there is a difference in features and which
feature is best in which plan. The
first and most important feature is room rent. Is there
any capping on room rent?
In the standard plan of ICICI Lombard Elevate plan,
you
get the option of a single private AC room,
but you
can also change it after taking a room modified plan. There are three options in it,
which we will understand in the add-ons section. Now let's
talk about Star Assure plan. Here
also the room rent has been divided into three segments,
according to your sum insured.
If the sum insured in your Assure plan is
₹1 lakh, then its %
i.e. if it is between ₹5000000 to
₹1 lakh, then you
can choose any room rent category except suite or above category during treatment. And if your sum
insured is more than ₹25 lakh, then you can
choose any room rent category.  There is
no capping on the room
rent you can avail. There is no room rent capping in the next variant of Aditya Bala Active One.
Within the standard plan itself, you get the option to choose any room.
Talking about day treatment, that is, treatments that do
not require 24-hour hospitalization,
are covered under all three plans and there is no
sub-limit in these. Now let's talk about
home care treatment and domicile
treatment. Domicile treatment means treatment at home.
When there is a compulsion, either the patient
's condition is not good enough to
go to the hospital or beds are
not available in the hospital, then
you can claim under domicile treatment.
You get the facility of domicile treatment in all three plans.
However, home care
treatment is when any such treatment which the
patient should have gone to the hospital for,
but on his own will, he
wants to get it at home through a certified home care
service provider. You will not get such
facility of home treatment
in ICICI Lombard Elevate plan.
In the Star Health Ashor plan and the Aditya Birla Active One
Next variant, you
also get the facility of home care, which is a
part of the standard plan. Now let's talk about
pre and post hospitalization expenses. For
how many days do these plans cover these expenses? If we
talk about the ICICI Lord Elevate plan, then the expenses related to any treatment you have taken,
before admission, will be covered for 90 days
and the associated expenses for 180 days after discharge, be it
medical consultation, medicine expenses or
diagnostic tests, will also be covered.
If we talk about the Star Shar Plan, then the
number of days of pre-hospitalization is 60
days and the expenses of post-hospitalization will be covered for 180 days.
Whereas in the Aditya
Birla Active One Next variant, you can claim expenses of
90 days pre-hospitalization and 180
days post-hospitalization.
Now comes the turn of road
ambulance, it is covered as per actuals in all three plans, that is, there is
no  There is
no limit on the use of road ambulances. Let's
compare consumable bills.
Consumable bills are non-medical items
that are part of any treatment, but
their category is not non-medical. These
can amount to 10 to 15 to 20 percent of your total claim amount. So this is a very
important coverage. You will have to take the
Claim Protector add-on under the IIC Lombard Elevate plan, only then
your consumable bill
items will be covered. The
consumable bill items under Star Health's Asher plan
are covered by default, and similarly, you will have to
take the Claim Protect add-on under the Aditya Bala Active One plan. I am talking about this next variant.
Now friends, let's talk about
maternity vaccination and new born baby
coverage. These three plans
provide these facilities in maternity, in
which the expenses of child birth are covered. New born
baby coverage is from the time the child is
born till the age of 91 days.
Born
baby can be covered only under coverage
and after that there are also vaccination expenses
which will be covered in your health insurance plan
or not
under Elevate plan. Under ICICI Lombard Elevate plan,
you will have to take these on only then you
can cover them. Whereas under Star Asher
plan,
you can claim maternity expenses up to 10% of your sum insured. The
coverage charges for newborn baby are
also covered. Apart from this, you
get a separate sum insured which is a
part of your standard plan. Whereas
in Aditya Birla Active One Next variant, you will not get any such coverage.
Now friends, there is a very important feature called
Sum Insured. If you do not take a claim, then
your premium remains the same. There
you do not get any discount
but your sum insured keeps increasing.
Your insured amount increases, so
how will it increase in these plans? If we talk about
ICICI Lombard Elevate plan, then
here you get a guaranteed no claim bonus of
20% for one year if you have taken the policy.  If you get
renewed and don't make any claim,
your sum insured will increase by 20%. And
in 5 years, if you have five
claim-free years, then that sum
insured will double. Your sum insured will
double.
Why is it called a guaranteed cumulative bonus? Because if you make a
claim, this cumulative bonus does not
decrease. Similarly,
under the Star Asher plan,
you get a no-claim bonus of 25% for every claim-free year. You
get a cumulative bonus, but
in case of a claim, it will reduce. Whereas, in the
next variant of Aditya Barela Active, there is
no cumulative bonus facility within the standard policy. You will have to
take an add-on called
Super Credit. If you take Super Credit, then
your sum insured will increase by 100% for every claim-free year.
That is, if you buy the policy today and
you don't make any claim for the entire year, then
on renewal, it will double and the maximum
it can go up to five times the sum insured.
So, if you have five consecutive claim-free
years, then you will have six
times the sum insured. If you
take Super Credit Age on the
Aditya Barla Active 1 Next variant, the
next feature is equally important,
which is the restoration benefit.
In the ICICI Lombard Elevate plan, it is
called If Reset. If Reset
means unlimited times restoration
benefit. On the first claim, you will
not be able to use the amount of this reset benefit,
which is equal to 100% of your sum insured. However,
after that,
you get the reset benefit for every claim made,
which is called Infighting. Whereas
in the Star Assurer plan, you will continue to get 100% of the sum
insured as your age restoration benefit.
Here too, you will
get unlimited times restoration benefit. In the Aditya Barla Active 1 Next
variant, which is part of the standard policy,
the feature is called Super Reload,
which is very important. It has two benefits.
The first benefit is that
you can use it on your first claim,
hence your sum insured gets doubled.
Suppose I have a policy of ₹1 lakh and
I need an amount of more than 10 lakh in the first claim, then
your super reload
benefit will remain active on the first claim as well, that is,
you get double the sum insured amount from the first day itself.
After that,
you will continue to get the restoration i.e. super
reload benefit for unlimited times on any subsequent claim. Let's
talk about compassionate travel. Compassion travel
means when a family member is away from his family
and has to be admitted in an emergency hospitalization,
but no
immediate
family member is with him to take care of him, then you can
claim the travel expenses of any immediate family member from the insurance company under one policy. So,
you will have to take compassionate travel as an add-on in the ICICI Lord Elevate plan. You
can take it through Star A Plane.  It's
part of the standard plan, meaning it's
inbuilt.
You can also avail it as an add-on within the Aditya Barela Active One plan
and claim up to ₹10,000 for a
compassionate visit. When such a
claim arises, it's time to
understand OPD (
Outpatient Department) expenses.
When we go to see a doctor, we
only have a consultation, medicines, and tests,
but we're not admitted because the
treatment wasn't that serious.
Can such consultations be covered under these
plans? In the
ICICI Lombard Elevate plan,
you'll need an add-on
called Benefit for OPD coverage. After availing the Benefit add-on,
you can avail physical and teleconsultations. The
Star Asher plan does
n't have OPD coverage. However, in the Aditya Barela
Active and Next variants, you
can avail a teleconsultation add-on, allowing
you to seek telephone consultations
from online panel doctors. Is there
coverage for personal accidents?
You will get this feature in all these three plans. In the ICICI
Lombard Elevate plan and Aditya
Barela Active and Next variants,
you will have to take this feature as an add-on.
Whereas, there
is no such coverage in the Star Assure plan. Now
comes the turn to discuss preventive health checkup. What
happens now is that in every health
insurance policy, after completing one year,
you are given the facility to get some health tests done.
But now in some plans,
it has started being given as an add-on
because most of the policy holders are
not able to use this facility. So,
due to this add-on, they can also save this premium.
Like here,
in the ICICI Lombard Elevate plan and Aditya
Barela Active One Next variant,
you will have to take an add-on if you
want the facility of health tests in your plan.
But in the Star Health Assure plan, up
to a limit as per your sum insured, you can get your preventive health checkup done every
year for a limited amount,
which is also mandatory to be done at cashless labs.
Now, final in coverage and benefits  The
point comes to the air ambulance.
You will get the air ambulance facility in all three plans. In the IIC Lombard
Elevate plan, you will have to take an add-on,
after that you can get air ambulance coverage.
In the Star Health Assure plan,
you get air ambulance coverage up to 10% of your sum insured. However, there is
no such coverage in the Aditya Barla Active 1 Next variant. Now friends,
comes the add-ons section, that is,
what add-ons are given to you in all three plans so
that you can modify or customize your plan. So
first, let's understand the add-ons of the
next variant of the Aditya Barla Active One plan.
What are the important add-ons you can get here? The first
add-on is
Chronic Care. Once the
waiting period for the listed chronic diseases is
over, you
can cover them from day one, which means no
waiting period will be applicable on them. This
add-on for Chronic Care, this add-
on for Chronic Care, is
applicable only for listed treatments.  The
next addon is critical
illness. Friends, if a policyholder is diagnosed with any of the listed critical illnesses, the
sum insured chosen by the policyholder for this addon is paid to
them as a
lump sum. A full
benefit will be given to them so that they can get
treatment for this critical illness. Along with this, the
most important addon is super credit, in
which you can increase your cumulative bonus up to
five times. 100% every
claim-free year and the maximum limit is ₹
500, that is, you can increase your sum
insured up to five times through super
credit.
Now,
what is the sequence of use of your sum insured? First of all,
your sum insured, which is the basic sum
insured for the policy amount, will be
used. After that,
if you have opted for super credit, then its
money will be used. After that,
I told you about the super reload, which is the restitution benefit,
which is standard.  The money that is part of the policy will be
used and after that you can use the
money of Cancer Booster Cover which is the next add-on.
If you
take the add-on of Cancer Booster Cover in Aditya Berla
Active and Next variants, then
you get an amount equal to your sum insured on
diagnosis of cancer of a specific intensity. Now, to know what is this intensity and
which cancers it
is applicable for, you will have to refer to the policy wording
document. The
intensity of each type of cancer is written there
that if it is of this intensity, you
can use this money. Cancer Booster
Addon has only one use, that if
your sum in sum is reduced on diagnosis of cancer, then
you can use this additional sum in sum. The
next add-on through this add-on
is friends, Durable Equipment Cover. The durable equipment
listed in
Durable Equipment Cover are such
equipment which you can use for a long time,
whose life is a little
longer, if they  If medical treatment is also a part of the treatment, then
you can also purchase that with this add-on in
Aditya Bala Active and Next
variants. However, as I mentioned,
apart from this, you can also take coverage for personal accidental as an
add-on and along with this,
you can also reduce your waiting period by taking the add-on, whether
your waiting period is for a pre-existing disease
or a specific disease, you will be
able to reduce it. Along with this, if
you want to put a capping on room rent, then you
can also put a capping on twin sharing or single private AC room
after taking the add-on of room rent modification. However, there is no
capping on
room rent in the standard policy. Now friends, let us understand the
add-ons of ICICI Lord Elevate plan. The
first add-on is Ifna Care, that is,
lifetime, you
can take a claim up to an unlimited amount, that is, if
your policy has a fixed sum insured
and if you want that there should
not be any limit on a single claim in any lifetime sum.
If you have taken the add-on of Ifna Care, then
you can do this.
However, you will have to take this add-on in the first two years
only. You can either take it at the beginning of the policy
or choose it at the time of renewal of the first policy.
And if you are
taking a policy for two or three years together, then
you will have to choose it in the beginning itself. The
next add-on comes friends,
Power Booster. Your
cumulative bonus in Power Booster will keep increasing up to 100% every year
and there is
no limit on the maximum increase, that is, your cumulative bonus can
increase unlimited times, but
for this you will have to take an add-on called
Power Booster. The next add-on is Jump Start.
If you take Jump Start, then
you can get coverage for the six listed diseases which are medical conditions which are visible to you on the screen right now, from the 31st day.
You may also have to pay an extra premium for taking the Jump Start add-on. The
next add-on comes in Room Modify. You
can choose any room by choosing a twin sharing
room.  You can do this because single
private AC room is already a
part of the standard plan, apart from this the
company has also given a third option, you
can also choose the percentage based room rent limit,
if you can choose that then
you will get 1% of your sum insured as room rent
and you can claim 2% of the sum insured for ICU
treatment,
but if you modify your room rent limit then only the
waiting period can be
reduced, whether it is the
waiting period of your specific disease, whether it is the
waiting period of pre-assisting disease,
whether it is the waiting period of maternity, all
types of waiting periods can be reduced,
for this also you will have to pay extra premium
and many times this question also arises
whether loading will also be charged on reducing the waiting period, so
according to your assisting medical conditions some loading can also be taken in the premium i.e.
An extra premium can
also be charged from you. Apart from this, there are
maternity benefits under which
you can take coverage of child birth, coverage of new born
baby and you can
also take coverage of vaccination. You can also take B-Fit which
is an OPD rider,
under which you can
take advice from the doctor through physical and online tele-consultations for
any of your medical conditions.
Apart from this, personal accident and
critical illness are fixed benefit policies
under which if you choose fixed sum insured, then
on diagnosis of the listed critical illness or the personal
accidental benefits like
personal accidental death, permanent total
disability, permanent partial
disability, whatever your
amount is, then according to that the
policyholders will get benefits. Next add-on is
Claim
Protector. We had mentioned this earlier also
when we compared the difference of consumer bill items,
Claim Protector.  By taking this add-on,
your non-medical items will
also be covered under this plan. This
can be around 10 to 15 percent for each treatment. So you should definitely take this add-on. The
next add-on is durable
equipment cover. This is also similar to the Aditya Barela
Active One Next variant.
What is durable equipment cover? This is the
equipment that you can see on the screen right now,
which the patient can
use for a very long time,
such as a wheelchair, ventilator,
oxygen concentrator. You can
also get coverage for these types of durable equipment covers
in the Elevate plan through an add-on.
Now, if we talk about the Star Asher plan, there
is no extra add-on here. However, you can definitely choose the annual aggregate deductible
option of ₹5000000 and ₹1 lakh
here. Now, before
I tell you the gist of the comparison of these three plans, that is,
what do I need to know in comparison of these plans?  What did you like, what did you dislike,
what are the special features and shortcomings in each plan, let us
understand the waiting period of all these three plans once,
then after that we will discuss this topic comfortably, first of all the
initial
waiting period is of 30 days in all the three plans,
which is applicable
in all the plans, within the first 30 days
you will
not be able to file any claim except accidental claim, whether it is for
any sickness, illness or any other
medical condition, the
waiting period of specific disease i.e. slow
growing illness, their waiting period is also
24 months i.e. 2 years in all the three plans,
however in Aditya Barella Active One
Next variant and
in IIC Lombard Elevate plan, this 24
month time can also be reduced to 12 months,
for this
you will have to pay extra premium, now comes the turn of
waiting period of pre-assisting disease, so
in IIC Lombard Elevate plan,
that PD waiting period  The period is of 36 months,
you can reduce it to 24 months or
even 12 months
after paying extra premium. In Star
Health Assure plan,
your waiting period in the standard policy is 36 months,
but if you take LTP,
long term policy of 36 months i.e.
3 years, then the waiting period is
reduced from 36 months to 30 months i.e. 1 year
for pre-existing diseases. Now let's talk about
Aditya Birla Active One Next variant,
here the waiting period for pre-existing diseases
is 48 months i.e. 4 years, which can be reduced to
36 months, 24 months and
even 12 months, but apart from Aditya Birla Active
Next, in the higher variants,
this waiting period will already be 36
months. One point about modern treatments was left.
If we talk about modern treatments in coverage and benefits, then let
me clarify it in all the three variants,
i.e. Star Assure and Aditya Birla Active and
Next variants.  All
three treatments within the ICC Lord Elevate plan are
covered up to the sum
insured, and there is no capping for any treatment.
Now, friends, let's
find out what the special features of these plans are
and what shortcomings I see.
First, let's discuss the ICC Lord Elevate plan.
What is its biggest advantage? The
plan is very flexible.
You can choose the plans as per your wish. The
features are not forced upon you. It is possible that
some policyholders may
not need these features, so they can pick and choose and pay a
premium for them. Other
policyholders who do not need these add-ons will have to pay a
significantly lower premium. This gives
you an extra benefit in
that you can customize your plan accordingly.
Secondly, the
theme of inclusion within this plan is that
you can avail unlimited sum insured,
unlimited reset amount, which means
you can avail unlimited restoration benefit,
unlimited claim amount, and
unlimited collect bonus.  You can do this
through the Power Booster addon, so the
limits here have been expanded a lot
and an attempt has been made to increase the coverage as well.
Apart from this, there is no capping on the maximum entry age for
adults,
up to 125 years, which means adults can
take the policy, that is, there is no
limit here and the waiting period can also be
reduced, whether it is the
waiting period for maternity, pre-existing
disease or specific disease,
all these can be reduced, but
I see a problem here right now,
although this plan is new, it has just been
launched and whatever is being discussed about it right now is
document based
things, that is, only those things are there which are written in their policy coverage,
what kind of service the insurance company provides you,
how this plan is implemented, there are
some hidden shortcomings in this plan
which will come to light with time, which we
will discuss in future videos as well,
but for now, I feel one shortcoming here is that
if you port the policy, the insurance company  If you buy a policy,
you'll need to
take some compulsory add-ons. There are five or six such add-
ons that you must take, but if
you're buying a fresh policy, there's
no such compulsion. This is the only drawback
I see in it currently.
However, as time goes by, we'll learn more about your
experience and
what problems arise during claims.
Because there are no
problems at the time of purchasing the policy, the
problems with health insurance
begin at the time of claims. The real
picture comes to us only at the time of claims.
Now let's talk about Star Asher's
highlighted features, that is, what's
good about it. First,
you get unlimited restoration, which is
part of the standard plan.
You get quite good maternity coverage here.
Within maternity, there's
coverage for newborns, childbirth, and
vaccinations. You'll get all of that. Along with
this,
you can also cover one cycle of assisted reproductive treatments per year.
Treatments like IVF are also available.  After the waiting period,
you can cover these. Uterine fetal
surgeries are also covered, meaning
any surgery required inside the uterus before the baby is born is
also
part of the standard plan. So, if you are
searching for a maternity-related plan,
you can also consider the Star Assure plan.
Although Star Health's Women
Care is also a similar plan, which has
many maternity-related features,
but the Assure plan also provides overall coverage
for other family members. The
entry age for adults in the Star Assure plan is 75 years.
Although this is not less, if compared to these two
plans, where the
entry age here is unlimited and there is
no capping, in the Star Assure plan,
you will be able to take this policy for the maximum age of 75 years for the first time.
If you are porting the policy,
you can do it even after that. One
drawback that I found in the Star Assure plan is the
room rent limit. Now, there may be a
policyholder who has a
higher age limit.  There is no need for sum insured
because there is unlimited restoration, that
amount will keep coming to him. If an individual is
taking a policy for himself or a husband and
wife are taking a policy for themselves, they
live in a small town and if they
take a sum insured of ₹1 lakh, then
they will get room rent of only ₹1 lakh. So, this room
rent limit is up to ₹1 lakh.
If it had been extended to a single private room,
it would have been much better, but you
can avoid it, although your
premium will definitely increase.
If you choose a sum insured of ₹10 lakh instead of this, if
you take a Star Echer Plane, then
your minimum sum insured should be ₹10 lakh
because
I do not believe that the room rent limit of ₹1 lakh is correct. Now let's talk about the
next variant of Aditya Bala Active V.
What are the special features in it,
brother, first of all, there is no maximum entry age
limit. Even the policy holders on the higher side
want to take this policy.  You
can avail this. Apart from this, there are some add-ons which
make this plan very special. The first add-on
is Chronic Care, under which the chronic
listed diseases can be covered from day one.
If you want
coverage for these conditions from day one, then you can avail this
add-on and you will get
coverage from day one, but you will have to avail this add-on for
Chronic Care. Apart from this, Super
Credit is a very good feature, although it is provided as an add-on,
otherwise
you will be able to use only your standard sum insured.
If you avail Super Credit, then
after that your sum assured bonus can
increase up to five times. The next important feature
is Super Reload, which is a
part of the standard policy. Here, Super Reload is quite different from your
standard restoration benefit
because it has two features. The
first is 2 * Sum Insured.
You can use the Super Reload amount equal to the sum insured on the first claim in your policy,
and the next claim
fixes
up to 100% of the sum insured, i.e.,
on the first claim as well.  A sum insured equal to the sum insured
is available. Furthermore,
you'll receive a 100% restoration benefit on future claims for an unlimited number of times, which is
quite unique. Now, let's discuss the
shortcomings of this plan. Compared to the
Star Assurer plan and the ICICI Lord
Elevate plan,
maternity coverage is
missing. This means that maternity coverage is not
available in the Aditya Barla Active Next variant, either as an add-on or in the standard policy. If
you're currently taking a policy for your family
and want to include maternity benefits in the future, the
Aditya Barla Active Next variant
doesn't offer this feature. You'll have to face these limitations here.
If
you want maternity coverage, you can choose from the other two plans.
After sharing your opinion, please
also review the prices of all three plans.  Let's compare
which plan will be affordable for you. To find out,
I am taking a sample family size of
two adults and two children. The adults are
38 and 35 years old and the children are 12
and 9 years old. The 12-year-old son and the 9-year-old
daughter are their addresses. Their addresses are
Delhi, which falls under Zone A. If you have
zones under your policy, then your premium will be for Zone A.
If you live in smaller cities, then
your premium could also be Zone B or Zone C.
However, in the ICICI Lord Elevate
plan, Star Asher plan, and
Aditya Bala Active Next plan, there is
no zone-based payment. The only
difference will be in the premium. You
can get treatment done in any zone. So, first of all, let's
know the premium of the ICICI Lord Elevate plan. How much money will this family have to pay for a coverage of ₹1 lakh
at a Delhi address.
Now, in the
standard plan here, I had a room
modification
room, so I have modified the room
to any room and along with that, the power.
I have also added the booster add-on, so
if we add these two add-ons with the standard policy, then this family will have to pay a premium of
₹1,265 for a coverage of ₹1 lakh, that is,
₹1,265
annually. Whereas for the Star Asher
plan, this family will have to pay ₹9,619 annually for the same family size and same coverage.
And in Aditya Barela Active and Next variants,
I have added the add-ons of Claim Protect and Super
Credit. I have added these
to the standard policy and after that the
annual premium becomes ₹3,2593 annually for a coverage of ₹15 lakh.
So friends, till here we have
extracted the essence of all these three plans and
compared these three plans with each other.
Now your picture about all these three plans, about
coverage, about benefits, about
eligibility, about ads, about
every aspect must have become quite clear
and affordable too. Now you will be
able to check which plan will be cheaper for you among
these three.  However,
my purpose in making this video is to
create transparency for you
so that you can see all three plans from the same perspective
and compare which one is best for you.
Before buying any health insurance policy, do your
research because
I made this video today. These
plans may undergo some changes over time.
You may be watching this video after two months, and there may be
some updates. But
for minor updates or to understand other features,
you must do your research. I
hope this video has
created some clarity for you and
added some value to your knowledge.
If you agree with me, then to
show your love and support, you
can like the video and share it wherever necessary.
My agent brothers
can share it with their clients. If
they want their clients to
understand this difference, you can share it there too.
You will continue to receive such valuable videos in a timely
manner on the Insurance Impact channel.  If you have
not checked the past videos, then you
can go to the playlist and check out the important videos as well and if you have
not subscribed to the channel till now, then please do
subscribe to the channel brother, you
give so much love, you watch the videos,
so please subscribe as well, this lets us know
that we have got your support,
I Arvinder Singh, now I take your permission, I will take your permission
in the next video, till then take care of yourself,
stay happy and
stay healthy, Jai Hind